twibbon.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Twibbon

Thank you for visiting an online service (e.g. website or mobile app) that posts a link to this Privacy Policy, owned or operated by Twibbon. This Privacy Policy will provide you with information as to how Twibbon collects, uses, and shares information about you, including the choices Twibbon offers with respect to that information, and applies to your use of any service, regardless of how you access or use it. For certain services, there may be additional notices about information practices and choices. Please read those additional privacy disclosures to understand how they apply to you.

By visiting or otherwise using the service, you agree to the service's Terms & Conditions (<http://twibbon.com/terms>) and consent to Twibbon's collection, use, and disclosure practices, and other activities as described in this Privacy Policy, and any additional privacy statements that may be posted on an applicable part of the service. If you do not agree and consent, please discontinue use of the service, and uninstall service downloads and applications.

Twibbon is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this service, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this policy.

Twibbon may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 30 August 2016.

### What we may collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Contact information you provide when you create a campaign (your name and email address)
  * Basic Facebook profile information when you accept these permissions when logging into the Twibbon Facebook App (your name, Facebook ID, profile picture, age, gender and other public information)
  * Basic Twitter profile information when you accept these permissions when logging into the Twibbon Twitter App (your name, handle, bio, profile picture, tweets, followers and other public information)

When you visit this service, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, the location of your ISP and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use this data to monitor the use of this service, to gather information about the location of our users and for this service's technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms & Conditions.

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information for the following reasons:

  * In order for you to support a campaign on Facebook or Twitter, or to create a profile on Twibbon.com, or to start a campaign on Twibbon.com.
  * For internal record keeping.
  * To improve our products and services.
  * So we may provide you with quicker support.
  * To send you updates related to Twibbon or any campaign you have created.
  * To send you promotional information about 3rd parties which we think you may find interesting.
  * To send your Facebook or Twitter profile picture that we collect to 3rd parties only in these circumstances:
    * If you support a campaign by updating your profile picture on Twitter or posting an image to your Facebook profile.
    * If the campaign explicitly states that your Facebook or Twitter profile picture will be sent to a 3rd party.
      * This statement must detail who the 3rd party is.
      * The profile picture can only be limited to use for marketing purposes, and the statement must detail this.
    * If the 3rd party is affiliated with the campaign you have supported.
  * For special cases where we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms and conditions or may be causing injury or interference with our rights, property, our customers or anyone who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose information we collect when we believe, in good faith, that the law requires it.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

The data we collect is stored with an industry leading cloud provider within the US. All of our data is encrypted while it is at rest.

Additionally: 

  * For data in transit, industry-standard transport protocols between user devices and our data centers are used. These same protocols are used within the data centers themselves.
  * Detection and mitigation techniques are used to protect against DDoS attacks.
  * Servers have antimalware software installed.
  * Regular penetration testing is conducted.
  * Our cloud provider has a global incident response team which works around the clock to mitigate the effects of any attacks. These are backed by centers of excellence that fight digital crime, respond to security incidents and vulnerabilities, and combat malware.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

We also use cookies for remarketing and retargeting purposes. The services we provide may include advertisements, which may be targeted to you via data provided by third party services including Google.com, Twitter.com or Facebook.com.

Twibbon also makes use of Facebook and Twitter login, who store cookies that are required for us to allow you to support a campaign on Facebook or Twitter, or to create a profile on Twibbon.com, or to start a campaign on Twibbon.com. Both Facebook and Twitter have their own cookie policies which can be viewed at <https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/> and at <https://twitter.com/privacy> respectively.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website and user experience, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

Please contact us at [support@twibbon.com](mailto:support@twibbon.com) if: 

  * You wish to request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998 (a small fee will be payable).
  * You wish for us to restrict the collection or use of your personal information.
  * You wish for us to destroy any record of your personal information.
  * You believe any information we are holding about you is incorrect or incomplete.
